Simon Fraser University Faculty Association fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Standing and Ad Hoc Committees, 1963 - 1985; F-79-6; 1.49 m of textual records
  - University Affairs Committee, 1963 - 1981; F-79-6-8; 64 cm of textual records 1 sound recording
    - University Affairs Committee: Agenda and Minutes, 1970; F-79-6-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 79-18)
    - University Affairs Committee: Minutes, 1970 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 79-18)
    - University Affairs Committee: Agenda and Minutes, 1971; F-79-6-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 79-18)
    - University Affairs Committee: Annual General Meeting, 1970 - 1973; F-79-6-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 79-18)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1963 - 1967; F-79-6-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 79-18)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1968; F-79-6-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 79-19)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1969; F-79-6-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 79-19)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1969; F-79-6-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 79-19)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1969; F-79-6-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 79-19)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1969; F-79-6-8-0-12 (Archival box - standard 79-19)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1969; F-79-6-8-0-13 (Archival box - standard 79-19)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1969; F-79-6-8-0-14 (Archival box - standard 79-19)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1969; F-79-6-8-0-15 (Archival box - standard 79-19)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1970; F-79-6-8-0-16 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
      - University Affairs Committee: grievance, 29 June 1970; F-79-6-8-0-16-1 (Audio reel OBJ-2757, Audio cassette OBJ-3242)
        Sound recordings
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-79-item1, F-79-item2, R-79-6-8-48.1 (ref.), C-79-6-8-48.2 (ref.).
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1970 - 1974; F-79-6-8-0-17 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1971; F-79-6-8-0-18 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1972 - 1975; F-79-6-8-0-18.1 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-79-6-8-0-19 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Correspondence, 1978 - 1981; F-79-6-8-0-20 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Professional Ethics Subcommittee, 1978; F-79-6-8-0-21 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969 - 1970; F-79-6-8-0-22 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1973; F-79-6-8-0-23 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1971; F-79-6-8-0-24 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances - Behavioural Sciences Found., 1973; F-79-6-8-0-25 (Archival box - standard 79-20)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1975; F-79-6-8-0-26 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-27 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969 - 1970; F-79-6-8-0-28 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1968 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-29 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1971 - 1973; F-79-6-8-0-30 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1970; F-79-6-8-0-31 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1971 - 1974; F-79-6-8-0-32 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-33 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1970 - 1972; F-79-6-8-0-34 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1968 - 1970; F-79-6-8-0-35 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-36 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969; F-79-6-8-0-37 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969 - 1970; F-79-6-8-0-38 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1970; F-79-6-8-0-39 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1970 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-40 (Archival box - standard 79-21)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-41 (Archival box - standard 79-22)
    - University Affairs Committee: PSA, 1969 - 1970; F-79-6-8-0-42 (Archival box - standard 79-22)
    - University Affairs Committee: PSA, 1971; F-79-6-8-0-43 (Archival box - standard 79-22)
    - University Affairs Committee: PSA, 1969 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-44 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1966 - 1973; F-79-6-8-0-45 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances, 1969 - 1970; F-79-6-8-0-46 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances - Miscellaneous, 1974 - 1976; F-79-6-8-0-47 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - University Affairs Committee: Grievances - Psychology, 1969 - 1971; F-79-6-8-0-48 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
  - Miscellaneous Committees, 1966 - 1974; F-79-6-9; 7 cm of textual records
    Sub-series consists of records of miscellaneous committees and subcommittees of the Faculty Association. Includes correspondence, memoranda, and reports of the Faculty Participation in University Government Committee, Sabbatical Committee, Welfare Committee and others.
    - Faculty Participation in University Government Committee, 1966 - 1968; F-79-6-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - Grievance Sub-Committee - PSA, 1969; F-79-6-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - Sabbatical Committee, 1966 - 1971; F-79-6-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - University Act Committee, 1972 - 1974; F-79-6-9-0-4 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - Welfare Committee, 1968 - 1970; F-79-6-9-0-5 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
    - Welfare Committee, 1970 - 1974; F-79-6-9-0-6 (Archival box - standard 79-23)
- Publications, 1966 - 1991; F-79-7; 13 cm of textual records
  Series consists of publications produced by and about the Simon Fraser University Faculty Association. Includes faculty handbooks, newsletters, bulletins, press releases, articles, and the SFUFA Splash.
  - Publications - Handbook, 1966 - 1974; F-79-7-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 79-24)
  - Publications - Newsletter, 1966 - 1971; F-79-7-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 79-24)
  - Publications - Newsletter, 1972 - 1991; F-79-7-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 79-24)
  - Publications - Bulletin, 1976 - 1977; F-79-7-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 79-24)
  - Publications - Bulletin, 1978 - 1981; F-79-7-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 79-24)
  - SFUFA Flash, 1982 - 1986; F-79-7-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 79-24)
  - Press Releases, 1967 - 1971; F-79-7-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 79-24)
  - Articles, Print and Other, 1967 - 1978; F-79-7-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 79-24)
  - Faculty Information, 1966 - 1985; F-79-7-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 79-24)